Guide to the Office of International Students and Scholars Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of International Students and Scholars records
1956-1999
RU 162
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
166.5
(145 boxes)
The records consist of personnel records, student records, and other materials documenting international students, employees and faculty at Yale University.
Yale University. Office of International Students and Scholars
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-E (YRG 4-E), Records documenting international students and scholars at Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted to the office of origin only.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of International Students and Scholars (OISS) is responsible for the general welfare of international students, employees and faculty at Yale University. OISS serves as a resource on immigration matters for the Yale community and Yale's liaison to those federal agencies concerned with matters related to international students and scholars.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of personnel records, student records, and other materials documenting international students, employees and faculty at Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Students, Foreign -- United States; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Office of International Students and Scholars
- Student records, 1956-1985; Accession 1989-A-106
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to the office of origin only.
- Student records, 1977-1989; Accession 1990-A-103 (Box 1–7)
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Student records, circa 1972-1989; Accession 1990-A-132
- Student records, 1981-1988; Accession 1991-A-016 (Box 1–8)
- Student and scholar records, 1981-1993; Accession 1995-A-079 (Box 1–30)
- Permanent student completed files, 1984-1993; Accession 1996-A-037 (Box 1–16)
- Foreign student/scholar and permanent resident records, 1986-1994; Accession 1997-A-026 (Box 1–15)
- Foreign student/scholar and permanent resident records, 1972-1996; Accession 1998-A-036 (Box 1–22)
- Foreign student/scholar records, circa 1988-1998; Accession 1998-A-089 (Box 1–9)
- Student and scholar records, circa 1987-1998; Accession 1999-A-056 (Box 1–15)
- Records of International Students, Scholars, and Permanent residents, 1991-1999; Accession 2000-A-048